[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かぜ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "風邪"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しゅっちょう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "出張"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しゅっちょうします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "出張します"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おだいじ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "お大事に"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とびます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "飛びます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はこびます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "運びます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'もどします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "戻します"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ほし' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "星"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ひかり' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "光"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'そら' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "空"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おと' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "音"
    }
]